export const generalQuestions = [
  {
    question: " Are the Comments, DMs, Or Follows/Unfollows Automated?",
    answer:
      "  We use automation in our services; however, we are using it sparingly. We prefer to employ less intrusive methods that will contribute to the organic growth of your account. A prime example is the likes and Story views, both tested methods that enhance the visibility of your profile without risking getting your account suspended.\n",
    index: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Do you Offer Any Deals or Discounts for Registering Multiple Accounts?",
    answer:
      "At the moment, we have some special offers for multiple accounts. If you purchase our services for two accounts, you can benefit from a 10% discount. For four accounts, there is a 25% discount, and for ten or more accounts, you can benefit from a 40% discount",
    index: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is There any Risk of Being Suspended or Blocked from Instagram for Using Your Services? ",
    answer:
      "We guarantee you that your account will never be suspended or blocked due to our services. We offer real Instagram likes from active users on the platform. For this reason, your account isn’t at any risk of being suspended or blocked.",
    index: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Do the Likes You Are Offering Come from Real Users?",
    answer:
      "Yes, we make sure to provide likes by real users that are active on the platform.",
    index: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Do You Offer Any Other Services Along with Views, Likes, and Followers?",
    answer:
      "Right now, our services include only likes, views, and followers. However, there are future plans to expand our services in the following months. Please, visit our website to keep up-to-date with our services.",
    index: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Can I Divide the Likes your Provide Amongst Several of My Posts?",
    answer:
      "Of course, you can divide the likes among several posts. However, this is only possible for content that was published after you have registered for our services. With this feature, we offer you the ability to divide the likes into up to 15 posts. With this method, you make sure that all of your posts get the love they deserve, even when you don’t have the time to personally boost them. With a total number of 15 posts, you make sure that not one of them will be left behind.",

    index: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "Is it Possible to Work on Instagram?",
    answer:
      "It is possible to work and profit on Instagram. Below, you will find some useful tips that will help you get started. We will cover the topics of marketing on Instagram and how you can become an influencer.",
    index: 6,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the Best Way to Collaborate with Celebrities and Influencers?",
    answer:
      "The first step for a successful collaboration with celebrities and influencers on Instagram is that you need to find the ones that express your values and personality. If you do that, an influencer will provide you with much-needed social proof, which is the best way to promote your product or service. However, if you fail in collaborating with an influencer that is close to your brand image, their audience will just dismiss your product or service.\n" +
      "In case you are an influencer, you should also think similarly. There is no pressure for you to partner with brands that don’t represent your values. Your audience follows you because you are authentic and you stand for the things you promote. If you are disingenuous, then your image will suffer and you will lose a significant number of followers.",
    index: 7,
  },
  {
    question: "How to Establish an Unforgettable Brand?",
    answer:
      "Establishing an unforgettable brand is a sure way to get Instagram followers. When users find a brand they like, they will return for more. Below, you will find tips to build your brand, gain more followers, and increase your ROI. \n" +
      "•\tPost Frequently and Be Consistent \n" +
      "When you are building an Instagram account, you should always keep a schedule and be consistent. Don’t overthink what you are going to post. Make sure that you regularly publish new content and that you keep your posts consistent.\n" +
      "•\tBoost your Posts with Hashtags" +
      "Hashtags begin with the # symbol and they are used to find similar posts on Instagram and other social media. With these tools, you can help other users find and follow your account. With the right use of a hashtag, you can also become a part of your niche’s community and create one of your own.\n" +
      "•\tHost Giveaways" +
      "There is no denying that users love to enter giveaways. For this reason, social media are full of brands that host contests for various products. The only thing that you need to do is to ask your users to like, share, and follow the post of your giveaway. This simple strategy will dramatically increase the number of your followers with the minimum cost.\n",
    index: 8,
  },
  {
    question: "Is There a Way to Make my Posts Go Viral?",
    answer:
      "Social media platforms have millions of users and so, every successful post has the chance to go viral. However, you can’t know beforehand which post is going to get shared. Users are unpredictable and sometimes your quick posts become more successful than the ones you took the extra effort to create. Even though we can’t be sure of what makes a post go viral, there are certain trends that consistently bring a lot of shares.\n" +
      "Some posts that get always shared on social media are the following:" +
      "•\tMotivational and funny quotes" +
      "•\tMemes" +
      "•\tTutorials and DIY projects" +
      "•\tUnique and original photos" +
      "•\tFunny videos and fail compilations" +
      "•\tBehind the scenes footage" +
      "•\tUser-generated content" +
      "•\tSocial Media Challenges" +
      "One thing that you need to do no matter your posts is to always brand your images. This way, even if your post gets shared, all users will know that it’s your creation.\n" +
      <b /> +
      "Growing the Number of your Followers\n" +
      "Nevertheless, there is one thing that will definitely make your brand strong on Instagram and that is a huge number of followers. Nowadays, you can do that in multiple ways, by getting followers organically, by buying Instagram followers or buying Instagram likes. Buying your following should be the first thing on your list when establishing your brand. If you take extra care to create content that your audience is going to like and appreciate, then the number of your followers will constantly increase.\n",
    index: 9,
  },
  {
    question: "Will Working with An Agency Bring Me Better Results?",
    answer:
      "   Instagram doesn’t have any limits as to who can post on the platform. This means that everyone has the potential of becoming an influencer if he finds a way to attract users’ attention. For example, a teenager can gain a lot of attention by posting consistent content that users like, while a big company struggles to gain any traffic.\n" +
      "For this reason, companies that want to build a presence on Instagram, usually work with an agency that will help them grow their account. The agency has professionals that know how to make any account stand out from the competition and start gaining the audience’s attention.\n" +
      "•\tCan I buy Instagram followers as a Company?" +
      "As a company on Instagram, you face a lot of competition. In your case, an agency will give you the right solutions for your industry. The agency will create a plan for the development of and organic content that will boost your account. This way, you will learn how to gain followers and how to create content that gets likes. In addition to this, you can buy real followers and Instagram likes from Likes.io, the best agency that provides you with followers and likes. By doing this, you enhance your brand and create opportunities for more future sales. \n" +
      "•\tCan I get Even more Followers as an Influencer?" +
      "If you are an aspiring influencer, then you are probably thinking of new ways to get more Instagram followers. In this case, working with an agency is the best idea. They will guide you to buy real Instagram followers that will boost your account and your brand’s reputation.  More followers mean a greater engagement rate, and this also means an increase in your prices.\n",
    index: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the Reason Why I Am Losing Followers?",
    answer:
      "The Instagram algorithm periodically goes through the accounts of its users. They examine the accounts that other users marked as spam and sweep them. If some of your followers are accounts like this, you might notice a sudden drop in followers.  If you notice that this thing happened within 30 days after you have purchased our services, we will make sure to replenish your followers.",
    index: 11,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Is There a Way to Cancel the Followers That I Purchased from MakeTop?",
    answer:
      "All of the followers we provide you are real Instagram users. This means that we can’t transfer or remove them. If there are some individual accounts you wish to remove from your follower list, you can block them one by one.",
    index: 12,
  },
  {
    question: "What Can I Do if I Don’t Want Follower Replenishment?",
    answer:
      "If you wish to stop follower replenishment, you should let us know by sending an email at support@likes.io.",
    index: 13,
  },
  {
    question: "How Often Do You Conduct Follower Replenishment?",
    answer:
      "We make sure to conduct follower replenishment every 24 hours. Once we detect a follower drop, our system begins the process.",
    index: 14,
  },
  {
    question: "Is there a Limit to the Followers I can Buy?",
    answer:
      "There is no limit as to how many times you can purchase our services. However, the cumulative number of followers should not surpass 100,000 followers within 30 days.",
    index: 15,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Do I Need to Provide Your with Passwords And Credentials To Purchase Your Services?",
    answer:
      "The only thing that we require of your is your account’s username. You don’t have to provide us with your passwords or your other credentials.",
    index: 16,
  },
  {
    question: "How Can You Provide Real Likes from Real Accounts?",
    answer:
      "We have worked hard to build a large network to provide you with superior services. Our numerous contacts among Instagram users allows us to get you all the real likes and followers you need.",
    index: 17,
  },
  {
    question: "What Are the Payment Methods you are Accepting?",
    answer:
      "At the moment, you can settle your bills with Cryptocurrencies, Apple Pay, and all cards. Nevertheless, we are planning on introducing more payment methods in the future to add more convenience to you.",
    index: 18,
  },
];

export const billingQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What Are the Payment Methods you are Accepting?",
    answer:
      "At the moment, you can settle your bills with Cryptocurrencies, Apple Pay, and all cards. Nevertheless, we are planning on introducing more payment methods in the future to add more convenience to you.",
    index: 0,
  },
];

export const frequentQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Does Instagram know when I buy likes?",
    answer:
      "No, Instagram has no method of knowing the difference between natural likes and those you purchase. To the platform, all of these likes are legitimate and permanent. As such, there is no risk in using our services.",
    index: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy likes on Instagram for another account?",
    answer:
      "The best likes are accounts that will like your content and find it useful or interesting. One of the best ways to grow your account is by engaging with likes of accounts similar to yours, whether they are your competition, industry influencers or in closely linked fields.\n" +
      "All you have to do is give us a few accounts that have likes you think will like your content, then we target those specific demographics. Select the location and demographic of your desired likes and the hashtags they search for regularly, and we will do everything else to make sure you get your likes and engagement from the right place.\n" +
      "Of course, you can manually find new potential likes by searching for a location or hashtag and then seeing which accounts are suitable and relevant. This method is simple but slow, making it difficult to achieve long-term growth.",
    index: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Do you need my password?",
    answer:
      "Our priority is real organic growth, with real followers and valuable engagement. Long-term results are more important to us than quick wins. You can monitor the progress of your campaign to see how it’s going, but we can’t guarantee how long it will take to reach your target. When you buy Instagram likes the cheap and easy way with Likes.io, we can help you keep growth on track with the strategic increase I likes and Story views that keep your account authentic.\n" +
      "We care about providing high-quality social media growth, and with great posts from you, you can see results after just a few days.",
    index: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "How much will it cost you?",
    answer:
      "We’ve created the safest and most stable growth platform possible, but automation does have some risks. Any type of third-party use on Instagram can risk blocks and bans, but it’s not common at all. We’ve never had an account get banned.\n" +
      "We avoid using overly intrusive or spamming methods, and instead look to engage real accounts, and encourage them to engage with your posts. We are also experts at staying on top of every Instagram update and requirement, so we can minimize risk as much as possible.",
    index: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the delivery time?",
    answer:
      "On every social media platform, people like following accounts that are popular. Just as how people like eating at restaurants with lots of customers, they want to be part of something tested - this idea is known as ‘social proof’.\n" +
      "Buying likes on Instagram is a great way to boost the ‘social proof’ of your posts, as the more likes you send, the more likely you are to get return engagement. By using Likes.io to buy likes for other posts, you can increase the visibility of your account and grow your followers organically.\n" +
      "Manually finding and scrolling through hundreds of relevant accounts will take up a lot of your time. Instead of concentrating on your core business objectives, you’ll be flicking through Instagram trying to find good accounts to like and engage with. Likes.io removes this time burden and provides a much easier way to use Instagram.\n" +
      "Our services can grow your popularity and enhance your reputation, giving you and your brand the platform you need to meet business goals. Buying Instagram likes with Likes.io leads to a stronger audience and a more engaged community.",
    index: 5,
  },
  {
    question: "Are bought Instagram likes real?",
    answer:
      "Yes, it’s fast and easy. Just give us your account name, explain your growth goals, and we’ll do the rest.\n" +
      "Once we have the demographics, locations, interests and hashtags of the people you’d like to follow your account, we can do the rest. Just monitor your growth campaign on our platform and see how quickly your social presence can develop.\n" +
      "If you want to share your brand with the world, paid Instagram engagement is a great way to get started, as it is timely and strategic. You’ll see your followers and your engagement steadily begin to rise, which starts to attract the interest of other users.",
    index: 6,
  },
  {
    question: "Can I lose the likes I bought?",
    answer:
      "Yes, it’s fast and easy. Just give us your account name, explain your growth goals, and we’ll do the rest.\n" +
      "Once we have the demographics, locations, interests and hashtags of the people you’d like to follow your account, we can do the rest. Just monitor your growth campaign on our platform and see how quickly your social presence can develop.\n" +
      "If you want to share your brand with the world, paid Instagram engagement is a great way to get started, as it is timely and strategic. You’ll see your followers and your engagement steadily begin to rise, which starts to attract the interest of other users.",
    index: 7,
  },
];

export const instagramLikesQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy Instagram likes? ",
    answer:
      "Buy likes of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and gain popularity." + "\n" +
        "An idea that first allowed passionate and enthusiastic photographers to post their photos online and share them with the world later became the most significant phenomenon in the social media industry, Instagram!\n" +
        "\n" +
        "With over a billion monthly active users and almost every famous person worldwide on its platform, Instagram has created its little haven.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Instagram is cited as the \"defining app of the last decade\" primarily because it was launched primarily in 2010, unlike Facebook and YouTube. This great app started as a completely different idea. Young Kevin Systrom (co-founder of Instagram) enjoyed the taste of whiskey and bourbon and decided to create an app based on his interests. He named it \"Burbn\". This app then became what we know today as Instagram.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It is almost impossible to stay away from social networks in today's high-tech world. The rapid growth of the possibilities and tools offered by social networks has made it irresistible for all industries to go online and be part of this revolution.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Everything is on Instagram, from big business, fashion, and entertainment to up-and-coming influencers. The reach that Instagram provides has never been seen before. The app's simplicity makes it easy for users to view and for businesses to set up a beautiful display.",
    index: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Why buy likes on Instagram?",
    answer: "Instagram is an ocean of possibilities. It can be the factor that allows you to quit your tedious 9 to 5 job and do whatever you like. Whatever your interests are, you can turn them into assets if you do it right. On Instagram, you can make money on anything.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Want to boost your Instagram account? Are you ready to make a career out of your hobby? Then you have found the right place. Here you will find out where people buy likes for Instagram, the pros and cons of it, and how Instagram might respond to this activity.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Running your profile and initially growing your account can be a lot of work. It takes people longer to acquire the first few thousand followers than it takes them to reach a million.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "A few years ago, people had no choice but to wait for months and years and continue to increase their bills slowly and steadily. In addition, there was not much competition then. That is why we have seen very few Instagram influencers and social media celebrities before.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "A lot has changed since then. Our society is moving faster than ever before. You do not have much time to wait and slowly gain followers. It would help if you did this as soon as possible. Otherwise, someone else will take your place.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "For these reasons, people have come up with new strategies to get more followers and get the most likes possible on their Instagram posts. Some of the main methods that rising Instagram influencers and brands use are:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "They create several fake Instagram accounts themselves and make these accounts follow them.\n" +
        "They hire a service that provides bots or fake followers to follow their accounts, like their posts, and comment on them.\n" +
        "Many influencers use the \"follow to follow\" strategy where they create and join multiple groups where members follow each other, like each other's posts, etc.\n" +
        "Influencers and brands buy Instagram likes and followers, which are real accounts on social media marketing services, and this helps them grow.\n" +
        "Among these methods, the first three are downright ridiculous. The fourth option is more or less viable. The first way to create many fake Instagram accounts and then make them like your Instagram posts is very tedious. And according to the second method, even a child can see this trick. Bots and fake followers will not fool anyone.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The third way is frankly unreliable. There is no guarantee that these people will continue to follow you or like your posts. And not to mention that it is even more tiring than the first one.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The fourth is the best strategy you can use of the four without exposing yourself to huge risks.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Buying cheap Instagram likes is a great way to increase the reach and engagement of your Instagram account. It can help you skip the initial chores and get your account up and running very easily. Now, two main groups of people are demanding a lot of followers and engagement on their Instagram accounts. Influencers and businesses on Instagram.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Instagram for influencers",
    answer: "Doing work, you love can improve your mental health and emotional stability. On the other hand, if you're stuck in a profession or job you don't like, it can seriously affect your mental health. If you have a passion for something and are great at it, why not make it a profession! You ask how?\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Well, Instagram! Let's say you learned how to pack and dress. Everyone always compliments the way you dress and the way you look. And you love it. You know very well how to apply makeup and what products to use or not use. You can use your talents and set up an Instagram account to post makeup tutorials. You can share your wardrobe or tell people what's trending this season.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Many people struggle to find the perfect look. Many people do not know how to apply makeup and what cosmetics to use. They are always looking for advice on Instagram. You can help these people with your informative posts and tutorials. You can influence people to dress nicely. And that's how you become an Instagram influencer.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "But it will take a long time to get to the point where your account is big enough to make a profit. It takes people longer to get a few thousand followers than it takes them to get a million.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "When you are just starting, the best way to increase your followers is through engagement with your posts. Instagram loves when your posts get a lot of views. Likes, Shares, Saves, and Comments count as interactions.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "So when you buy Instagram likes for your posts, it increases the engagement of your posts; hence, Instagram will promote your post to more and more people. This way, many people will be able to find your account and become your followers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "If you purchase likes for your Instagram account, it helps your Instagram account grow organically.",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Instagram for business",
    answer: "First introduced as a simple photo-sharing app, Instagram got a lot bigger. Today, Instagram is all about business. According to Instagram, about 80% of Instagram users follow a business account. Why not be yours.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Instagram provides many tools to manage and grow your business on its platform. It is easy to set up a simple business account for any business. Using Instagram for business is also profitable. You don't need an entire team to run a successful business.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You can attract many clients to your Instagram business account and expect your followers. You can also triple the traffic to your website or mobile app and even more with Instagram.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "But first, you will need to raise your account to a certain level. You can get likes for Instagram from us to increase the activity of your posts and grow your account organically.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Buying likes for Instagram can help you:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Reach more people and get more followers.\n" +
        "By getting more subscribers, we ensure social well-being.\n" +
        "Social proof provides more vital and more reliable consumer trust.\n" +
        "When a person sees that your account has more followers and your posts have more interactions, they are more likely to buy your product or service.\n" +
        "Having public engagements and following will also help you reach more people.\n" +
        "You can get more funds to spread your business widely.",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Who needs a boost of likes?",
    answer: "Targetologists recommend that business owners, bloggers, influencers, and owners of personal pages pay attention to cheating. You can get likes without logging in by adding a link to your profile!\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Cheat allows you to draw more attention to the products on the page. Photos with store offers with a lot of hearts inspire trust among users. People tend to think in groups. It seems to them that if a thousand people liked something on the Internet, then this thing is unique and attractive. This fuels interest in her.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It's worth getting likes on Instagram for a post if you:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "blogging;\n" +
        "sell goods;\n" +
        "develop your brand;\n" +
        "offer services;\n" +
        "are engaged in information business;\n" +
        "work as a model.\n" +
        "This is a sure way to quickly increase the number of marks under the publication and gain the audience's trust. You can always be sure that people will see your post with our service.",
    index: 5
  },
  {
    question: "Is it safe to cheat likes?",
    answer: "Cheat likes on Instagram are safe if you use them wisely. We do not share your data: be calm about your privacy. Your account will not be hacked or stolen.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Do not get carried away with cheating if you have few followers on your profile. It is essential to maintain a balance: the number of hearts should not exceed 30% of the subscribers. If you have 1 thousand subscribers and 900 likes, this will raise questions from users.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "This discrepancy can cause distrust in your audience, as well as in the Instagram system itself. A social network can restrict your actions or even block your account for excessive suspicious activity. However, you have nothing to fear if you act carefully and do not wind up millions of hearts at once.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You are getting:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "fast winding speed;\n" +
        "quality likes;\n" +
        "convenient site interface;\n" +
        "detailed statistics.\n" +
        "With us, you cannot worry about the security of your data and access to the page.",
    index: 6
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy IG likes cheap?",
    answer: "You can buy cheap likes on Instagram only on Maketop, where you can get a good result for even a small financial investment. The account will receive an instant increase in likes under publications and will very soon become one of the most popular at no extra cost.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Registration on Maketop is reduced to a minimum so that each user can quickly start getting likes. We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy Instagram likes crypto.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Buying 100 likes on Instagram on Maketop will cost mere pennies, and the result will pleasantly surprise you.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Advantages of Maketop - the best promotion service\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Free services without any restrictions and obligations to replenish the balance.\n" +
        "A quick boost of Instagram likes, which will be the envy of all your familiar Instagrammers.\n" +
        "Technical support will not leave the client in difficulty day or night.\n" +
        "Discounts on the purchase of points will make it possible to promote your Instagram account and save money.\n" +
        "Likes only from real users.",
    index: 7
  },
  {
    question: "How do hashtags work, and why do they need likes?",
    answer: "Hashtags have been used for a long time, even before the advent of Instagram. Their value lies in the fact that any user of a social network can quickly find all the latest posts on their request. Photos marked with a hashtag appear on the screen of the user's gadget immediately after he has entered his query into the search engine.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The number of likes under a hashtag post can significantly move the seat up, so more people will see the photo. Hashtags are a good tool for promoting your Instagram account, and experienced Instagrammers never forget about it, supplying their photo creations with various tags.",
    index: 8
  },
  {
    question: "Instagram deducting likes?",
    answer: "What always stops users when they are offered a cheat? It's not a waste of time or money to buy Instagram likes or earn points. It is the fear that the administration of the social network will write off the twisted likes, and the user will be left with nothing.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "First, you need to understand why likes or subscribers are being written off. Many programs and services on the Internet offer fast promotions for a relatively inexpensive fee. But the catch here is that the acquired likes will turn out to be fake, affixed from one-day pages.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Our service has a totally different approach to account promotion. All our users are real people who want to promote their page. They will not disappear with the onset of a new day, so their likes remain under publications forever. Only from us can you buy live likes on Instagram and not be afraid of their write-off.\n" +
        "\n",
    index: 9
  },
  {
    question: "It's time to make a decision - Buy Real Instagram Likes",
    answer: "Of course, this may seem problematic. After all, Instagram algorithms study many additional factors. They monitor the rate of content and the number of likes. If you decide to buy Instagram likes from Maketop, the process will be much more comfortable and quicker. It won't take you months or years to make a post popular. Your publication will become trendy within a few hours, and it will quickly pay off.",
    index: 10
  }
];

export const autoLikesQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy automatic Instagram likes?",
    answer: "Buy auto likes of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your channel popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Automatic likes on Instagram are considered one of the most effective and fast account development mechanisms. The social network algorithm considers not just the number of hearts but also the speed with which they appear. The quicker the post collects sympathy, the more interesting it is to the public, and the higher its place in the ranking. Boost Instagram Auto likes are likes that are automatically placed on each new post of yours and are designed to display publications in the TOP Instagram since this social. The network considers the speed of adding likes, and the higher it is and the more likes, the higher the chances of getting into the TOP Instagram.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Why do people buy automatic Instagram likes?",
    answer: "Not all users receive \"Like\" in the usual way; many use special programs that help to wind up the required number of \"hearts\".\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The application will offer to buy the required number of likes for a specific price for a lazy user.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "There are several categories of people who wind up likes on their pages on social networks most often:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "1. Young people are striving for rapid popularity.\n" +
        "Men and women, who have not yet managed to gain a sufficient number of friends on the social network, and those who have more than enough friends, wind up likes.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "When asked why they need so many likes, the answer is straightforward - they don't like a photo without hearts.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Business owners who decide to promote it on social media.\n" +
        "Usually, the more users speak positively about any goods, services, or offers; the more these offers are credible. Likes often replace positive reviews.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Contestants.\n" +
        "Today, you can often find various contests on social networks. You need to score the maximum number of reviews or \"likes\" on any entry to become a winner.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Autolike Instagram is the \"I like\" mark put on new publications in your IG profile in the desired amount already in the first minutes after posting. Many users of social networks are wary of services, sites, and programs that artificially increase resources. As practice shows, absolutely in vain. With a competent approach to choosing a service provider, you can achieve the desired indicator on the counter and the desired audience coverage without risks.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Auto-like Instagram posts - efficient, fast, reliable!",
    answer: "Quite often, quickly winding up likes on Instagram is not enough. Sometimes it's about the time of publication; sometimes, it's about the specific product that the promoted publication advertises. Such situations can be called a missed moment. And the universal tool, in this case, is automatic likes for new posts on the Instagram account and visits on Instagram.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "However, do not forget about the \"smart\" social network algorithms that consider the social activity. These restrictions are neglected by all kinds of free services and cheat programs. Our service uses exclusively safe promotion mechanisms within the current Instagram limits. Your posts collect hearts at an incredible rate, which, however, does not harm the account. For this reason, the \" Buy Instagram Auto Likes\" service and video views on Instagram are so popular and are ordered by dozens of users every day.",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Auto promotion Instagram",
    answer: "Instagram is a popular app for sharing photos and short videos. It is one of the few social networks that do not block ads.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The number of Instagram followers is growing every second. Therefore, it would be a reckless mistake not to use such a \"live\" platform to promote your business.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Instagram auto boost with the help of an automatic service will allow you to significantly increase the number of active followers in a short time. If done correctly, an advanced account will become a source of ever-growing income or a means to achieve other goals. Advertising of goods and brands can bring money, and it is ordered only from owners of promoted profiles. Starting your own business on Instagram is also a great idea.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Auto cheating Instagram followers through a proven specialized service with round-the-clock support is a great way to get a broad audience. Using this method, you are guaranteed to find yourself in the desired position in a short time. Investments are required, but our services are cheap.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy Instagram auto likes with crypto",
    index: 4
  }
];

export const instagramFollowersQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Need to buy Instagram followers?",
    answer: "Here you can buy real followers at reasonable prices and grow your Instagram popularity.\n" +
        "The debate about who is cooler - Vkontakte or Facebook has not subsided yet. While the opponents were giving their logical arguments, a new service appeared on the network, which collected all the best from VK, FB, and YouTube. Those of the users who turned out to be the smartest were seriously interested in the opportunity to buy Instagram followers and get likes.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "By the way, it is easier with likes - friends and acquaintances can help with them. Of course, each user wants to see many positive marks, but it is better to have more subscribers and fewer likes than vice versa.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Instagram, after its appearance, immediately began to lure the audience from other social networks. People were willing to create pages on Instagram, in large part because they liked the simple posting format. And really, what could be easier than photos with short text?\n" +
        "\n" +
        "In the past, you could be criticized for posting too many photos, but with the advent of Instagram, the game rules have changed. To gain popularity, you need to add as many interesting photos and short videos as possible (such an opportunity appeared over time).\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Moreover, as you might have guessed by now, if people are used to looking at pictures all the time, they will be more receptive to ads. For this reason, many stars and even companies use Instagram to make them known or gently remind them about the presence of their brand.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who are followers on Instagram?",
    answer: "Subscribers exist in any social network. Instagram followers are followers who become followers when they press the coveted button on your page. It means, that the person liked you or your posts and wants to follow your updates.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Logically, the cheating of Instagram followers solves several problems at once. Firstly, you get a base of followers who will initially give views simply because your posts appear in their feed. Secondly, you will get a certain number of likes from them, which will also increase your chances of taking better positions at the TOP.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "So, you learned that subscribers are essential and helpful people on your page and understood how they could help in certain cases.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Buy Real Instagram Followers : why is it essential?",
    answer: "Competition on Instagram is becoming more severe every day, so users in the struggle for favor use all ways of profile promotion. Experienced promotion and buying followers on Instagram allow you to gain live followers quickly and improve activity on your account.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "A promoted Instagram account is a significant way to self-realization; it increases your authority but is also a useful way to earn money. The more popular the account, the more comfortable it is to promote different services and products.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Both newcomer bloggers and celebrities with a multimillion-dollar audience try to buy 1000 Instagram followers. Ellen DeGeneres, Kourtney Kardashian, Miley Cyrus, and other stars do it regularly.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Why do you need to buy followers on Instagram?\n" +
        "So, you have decided to buy live followers on Instagram. It will give:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Increasing self-esteem. Many users recklessly ignore this bonus, thinking that they already love themselves very much. However, there is never too much self-respect. To amuse self-esteem without harm to others is great.\n" +
        "Business support. Dark times can come in business in just a couple of days. It is necessary to show stamina and not commit rash acts. It is also desirable to have some kind of weakly consumed or completely renewable resource. For example money, popularity, and valuable connections. An Instagram profile can be such a resource, with the help of which you can advertise your own business for free.\n" +
        "Your leisure time will become better. Who doesn't love a good vacation? Despite the general understanding of the need to relax with the greatest efficiency, people somehow ignore the basic principles of such relaxation. But you can share your impressions with other people, compete with them or plan joint leisure time, discussing your favorite hobbies!\n" +
        "You will contribute to self-development. Using the opportunity to buy Instagram followers - you can use the page to communicate with interesting people, for self-expression, and maybe even for work!\n" +
        "You will get new opportunities for earning. Give yourself a chance and try to make money on advertising or use your account to promote your services and products. It is possible!",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Buying Instagram Followers: Benefits of Choosing",
    answer: "You can treat social networks differently. But judging by the number of users who want to wind up followers on Instagram, the importance of these resources for modern people cannot be underestimated.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Moreover, many Internet users can no longer imagine their existence without their favorite social networks and along with the traditional morning cup of coffee, start their day by checking the page for new comments and fascinating entries in the feed.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It is worth remembering that Instagram is somewhat different from ordinary social networks. There are no text messages and materials here since this original resource is dedicated exclusively to photos. At the same time, given the real passion of many modern people to capture their lives in pictures and demonstrate them in the vastness of the virtual space, one can hardly be afraid that soon the fashion for photoblogs will go away forever.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Experts identify several main reasons why account holders resort to paid promotion of live followers on Instagram. First of all, it is the desire to increase the authority of your account. The presence of a large number of live followers on Instagram automatically means that this photo blog contains interesting information worthy of attention.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It doesn't matter if the fast gaining of followers on Instagram is connected with your desire to realize your personal ambitions or the desire to promote your business account. When you get real followers on Instagram in large numbers, it always brings positive results.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Since the competition in the blogosphere is incredibly high, the decision to buy live followers on Instagram is a smarter and faster option than collecting followers through conventional methods. Even if your pictures are really interesting and unusual, it will take time to get 1000 followers on Instagram because the number of accounts in any niche is simply impressive, and it is very difficult for beginners.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "By deciding to get followers on Instagram online, you will be able to boost your page in a short period of time and take high positions in the ranking. For example, cheating followers on Instagram through our website will allow you to multiply the number of your followers in just a few days!\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Artificial cheating of followers on Instagram leads to the fact that ordinary visitors begin to pay attention to your photoblog and subscribe to it! When an account reaches the TOP, it immediately becomes noticeable and arouses interest among users. Thus, subscribers on Instagram for money lead to you and free followers because here the well-known stereotype from the category “where everything is, I go there” is triggered.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "When a person notices that you have a lot of real followers on Instagram, they will probably want to follow or at least bookmark your page to study it more closely in the future. For most social network users, it is psychologically difficult to ignore those who have 1000 followers on Instagram or many times more, and new subscriptions contribute to further promotion of the account and growth in popularity!",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Why is the TOP of Instagram occupied by accounts that buy followers?",
    answer: "As you already understood, many users easily guessed where to buy Instagram followers and understood how to make money on it. Moreover, we have already talked about the direct connection between the TOP of publications and the number of subscribers on your page.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The fact is that each publication has its internal rating in the social network. It depends on the number of followers and likes. As a result, it turns out that to start participating in the race for a place in the TOP, you need to have as many of these indicators as possible.",
    index: 5
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy followers on Instagram quickly and safely?",
    answer: "Increasing live followers on Instagram is an effective mechanism for promotion on this social network. Regardless of the purpose for which you buy followers, keep your safety in mind. Special attention is paid to new Instagram accounts, and for extreme activity, you can get banned. Here are some life hacks to help you stay out of trouble:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Restrictions. The policy of the social network is against any cheating and strictly monitors this. So don't be in a rush to buy 1 million Instagram followers on the first day you create a page. You won't even be able to gain 1000 followers as the page will be eternally blocked. It is secure to buy 500 Instagram followers per day if your page is less than six months old.\n" +
        "Choice. Do not use other services. If you trusted our poprey.com to buy 1000 Instagram followers, do not go to other sites! Instagram tracks logins from various devices to control account hacking. And each service asks you to enter your profile. If you use several services, then there will be several inputs. The social network will notice this and will not leave it unattended;\n" +
        "Filling. Before you buy 5000 Instagram followers, fill in the description, upload an avatar, and add links. Remember that even the best Instagram followers won't last long on a faceless profile.",
    index: 6
  },
  {
    question: "When is it recommended to wind up live subscribers?",
    answer: "Always. And if the owner of the page determined to order the service, then the cheating of subscribers will not necessarily be carried out at the expense of the cheapest audience. Accounts that have gained fake followers with empty profiles are not highly valued on the social network. Don't expect posts to come first on the list. Some pages are simply banned for such actions.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You need to wind up only live subscribers. There are several reasons for this:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "ensuring interest from the target audience;\n" +
        "attracting subscribers and gaining their trust\n" +
        "The more live subscribers you have the higher the interest in the page and the potential advertiser. The owners of popular channels with thousands of subscribers receive decent money for advertising.",
    index: 7
  },
  {
    question: "The secret of popularity. How to buy followers on Instagram?",
    answer: "Finally, gaining followers quickly on Instagram is a great way to fulfill your ambitions and stand out from the crowd. Buying subscribers, a person attracts the attention of a huge number of users, quickly becomes widely known, amuses his pride, and reaches high positions in the ranking of the most popular users\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Many people post photos of their luxury vacation, new car, and meals from expensive restaurants on the Internet for the sole purpose of showing off. For the same reason, they need a large and even huge number of subscribers - to wipe the nose of a rival girlfriend or show off in front of colleagues (or classmates).",
    index: 8
  },
  {
    question: "Maketop is the best site to buy Instagram followers",
    answer: "Stop bothering about where to buy Instagram followers! You have already landed on the site of the best organic audience providers. Here are 5 causes why Maketop is the best place to buy Instagram followers:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Execution rate\n" +
        "We work only with a live target audience. No bots, bans, or passwords. To buy real Instagram followers, you just need to enter a link to your Instagram\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Instant start\n" +
        "Launch within 5 minutes after buying subscribers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Secure Collaboration\n" +
        "To buy Instagram followers, you do not need to provide us with your login details.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Support 24/7\n" +
        "Our managers are constantly ready to answer your questions about followers on Instagram. You can call both on weekends and at night.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Convenient payment methods\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy Instagram followers with crypto. Everything is as fine and convenient as possible.",
    index: 9
  },
  {
    question: "Why buy Instagram followers for business?",
    answer: "Business promotion on Instagram allows you to create a brand and company image and point out the powers of the company and how it differs from competitors. A promoted profile on a social network allows you to obtain feedback from clients, and present new products. Through Instagram, it is easier to bring customers to the company's website.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "One of the most effective ways of advertising through a social network is word of mouth. It is particularly in demand in the service sector. Showing the results of the work of a hairdresser or photographer, posting a photo of the interior of a cafe or restaurant is a simple and effective way to attract new customers. Organic promotion of a business account will take months, so at the start, you just require to purchase at least 10 thousand followers on Instagram.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The circuit would then work like this:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "the service brings new followers to your Instagram page;\n" +
        "a large number of subscribers leads to the growth of the account; it begins to attract the attention of other users;\n" +
        "people interested in buying goods or services subscribe to your updates;\n" +
        "sales are on the rise.\n" +
        "It’s not enough if you only sell rate products or services at a high level; word of mouth will work, thanks to which potential buyers will flow to you like a river. In such a straightforward and uncomplicated manner, you can promote large online stores and small shops or services of private entrepreneurs.",
    index: 10
  },
  {
    question: "Cheat followers on Instagram online to participate in contests",
    answer: "Instagram is a social network for young and active people, so online Instagram followers will come in handy for those who want to be not just a passive contemplator, but take an active part in the life of the resource.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "First of all, we are talking about numerous contests. To get the victory is much easier if you buy real followers on Instagram and enlist their support when voting. Contests on Instagram are held regularly and participation in these events is a great way to express yourself and win valuable prizes from the organizers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It is enough to buy a suitable tariff plan on our website, and getting followers on Instagram will allow you to multiply the number of likes for your photos. It is completely natural that the winner of any contest is the owner of the biggest number of likes, and it is possible with a large number of followers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Cheating live followers on Instagram on your own is problematic. It is better to buy a suitable Maketop service package and watch how the number of followers increases day by day.",
    index: 11
  },
  {
    question: "Live subscribers are vital!",
    answer: "Dubious services offer promotion through the signature of bots, not real people. The distinction between them is noteworthy. A bot is a robot, a program that performs certain actions according to a given algorithm. It is quite capable of following, getting likes on Instagram, and small comments under posts.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "To complete the task, special accounts are used that do not have publications and subscribers. They simply create the appearance of activity and subscribe to various channels. As a rule, such \"false followers\" are inexpensive - 10k bots will cost 5-10 times cheaper than live users.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Live subscribers are real people who:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Are interested in the content of your Instagram page.\n" +
        "Earn real money for following other people's Instagram accounts.\n" +
        "The last category is also represented by real people who have an active page with publications, avatars, and even subscribers. Such offers do not always become regular customers but provide passive assistance in their promotion. By subscribing to a page, users increase its popularity. This allows you to attract an interested audience, which is only a benefit for the channel owner.",
    index: 12
  },
  {
    question: "Is it possible to earn on a promoted account?",
    answer: "When it comes to big earnings, users almost immediately remember YouTube. It is understandable because everything is simple here - you need to come up with an idea for videos and earn money on views and advertising on the channel.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Instagram can also compete with YouTube because a popular account can be used to sell advertising and stimulate your own business.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "One of the factors affecting popularity is the number of followers on your page. The more of them, the more elite your account is considered, and the higher your chances for further development of the page and business.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "So, you can earn on your account:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Selling ads.\n" +
        "Advertising your products and services.\n" +
        "Using affiliate programs and collaborating with other users.\n",
    index: 13
  },
  {
    question: "How to get a lot of followers on Instagram yourself?",
    answer: "Do you want to have a lot of subscribers, but at the same time do not want to spend your hard-earned money? In this case, read our article to the end because we have collected the most effective methods for free promotion of Instagram profiles!\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Suppose you were able to buy followers on Instagram and you need additional followers but at the same time, you do not want to waste your money and take risks. In this case, do not use these methods:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Doubtful programs. In such software, targeting usually suffers, and user rights are often violated. In general, everything is bad.\n" +
        "Working with cheap software and bots. Here passions are already running high, but the effect is still difficult to achieve. The fact is that you need a lot of blank pages, you will also need certain skills in working with software, and you will also need to study the mechanisms of its work.\n" +
        "Mutual subscription. Another cheap way to get popular. The essence lies in the fact that you need to beg for subscriptions or wander through hashtags and subscribe to dubious personalities. All this is organized quite badly and is usually done by scammers who fill the indicators on the page for bad deeds.\n" +
        "Below we will describe the methods that you can use to ensure that your page flourishes and you do not run into trouble. Read carefully:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Working with hashtags Words that are not always distinguishable from the first time will help you to be quoted in the search for Instagram and other resources at different times. Do not ignore this tool.\n" +
        "Post-high-quality photos, work on their descriptions. It would be nice to learn at least the basics of professional photography and photomontage.\n" +
        "Use geolocation. Sometimes, buying followers on Instagram may not be necessary. It is enough to mark your position in the photo, and some people will find your profile through a global search on Instagram.\n" +
        "Apply to like and follow. Be the first to subscribe to interesting people and also leave likes and comments under their posts.\n" +
        "Organize contests, meetups, or Q&A videos. All this can be used to attract users to your page and encourage them to follow you.\n" +
        "Collaborate with other people. Feel free to exchange audiences and promote each other, as well as work on joint projects.",
    index: 14
  },
  {
    question: "Buying subscribers - are there any write-offs?",
    answer: "Having read our article up to this point, it’s a little hard to believe that everything can be so good, right? You have nothing to be afraid of; however, rumors about the danger of cheating did not arise from scratch. The fact is that social network filter settings change quite often and every day you have to check whether everything is in order with your accounts.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Unfortunately, not a single exchange could completely get rid of write-offs of followers. The best that many specialists have managed to do is to minimize losses. It is also necessary to understand that write-offs are of two types:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Write-offs within the service itself.\n" +
        "Write-offs from Instagram.\n" +
        "The worst thing is to fall under the Instagram filters because it will be almost impossible to protect the page. As for natural losses, they are within 10% of the total amount of subscribers. This percentage is normal, and in most exchanges, it starts from 15% and reaches 30%. We are also constantly working to reduce these losses to 1-3%, and in many cases, out of 100 subscribers, no more than 1-5 people can unsubscribe.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "To buy IG followers quickly and not fall under the filter, you need to do the following:\n" +
        "Keep posting. The most common problem among most social media account holders is overconfidence. A large number of new subscriptions cloud the perception, and it seems to users that they can now rest on their laurels, and the page will continue to untwist itself. This position is fundamentally wrong, and in any case, you will have to deal with your profile if you want to achieve a result.\n" +
        "Carefully increase the number of followers. Beginners sin by immediately throwing themselves into masters, winding up thousands and sometimes tens of thousands of subscribers. Such an order will not always have time to be completed because Instagram will ban you if you increase the number of followers too intensively. If you have already reached the number of several thousand - do not wind up more than 10% of the total number of subscribers per day.\n" +
        "Use different types of winding. A combination of different types of promotion is necessary to increase the effectiveness of each of them. The more ways you promote your account, the more difficult it is for Instagram to determine the fact of cheating.",
    index: 15
  },
  {
    question: "How to get followers on Instagram - ways",
    answer: "Many users are poorly versed in the types of buying and do not understand what is it for. Such a position will not lead to good - you need to understand as soon as possible how the sphere of promotion works. And fortunately, you are lucky - you are on one of the best services, where they will explain in detail what types of promotion are and how they differ from each other.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "So, if you want to buy Instagram followers cheaply or even get them for free, carefully read the information below.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Method 1: Buy likes on forums and websites. In this way, you can save a lot of money and even promote your page for some time without serious losses. Unfortunately, nothing lasts forever, and most often, Instagram will have claims against you that there will be no one to redirect. Because you collaborated with an anonymous user about whom you know absolutely nothing.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Method 2: High-quality promotion with Maketop. Service works on the principle of mutual exchange, allowing users to get likes on Instagram, followers, and comments on all social networks.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "To work in the service, you do not need to provide personal data, and even more so - access to your account! Most often, access to your account is required by scammers who are very likely to steal it from you under any, even the most plausible pretext.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We strongly recommend not to stop increasing the number of followers. To get the most out of Instagram followers, you also need to take care of likes, comments, and views.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Method 3: Ask friends to help you, use old pages. As you might have guessed, it is unlikely that you will be able to compete with professionals in promotion efficiency.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "However, you can pull up reserves in the form of old pages and “help from the hall”. If you are sociable and like to communicate, then you can safely write to your friends with a polite request to see your publications. You can also do this in other social networks, as if by chance, carefully weaving such \"advertising\" into the topic of conversation.",
    index: 16
  }
];

export const instagramViewsQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy Instagram views?",
    answer: "Buy real views of the highest quality here and make your account popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Now Instagram is in demand because there are many young people using it, and this is one of the largest platforms for promoting your page. Many people regularly publish their photos and short videos to collect as many likes as possible, which will allow them to get promoted in the shortest possible time.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "One of the most effective methods for PR content specifically on this network is just the same Instagram views and for most social networks, one of the most common methods to become more popular is to buy followers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "On Instagram, a like can completely replace viewing and creates an opinion about you in front of other users;\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The more views you have on photos or videos, the more they will attract people to watch them, creating the so-called crowd effect.\n" +
        "This type of advertising undoubtedly increases trust, as they become very aware of the quality of this content.\n" +
        "You can get to the top only thanks to a large number of views.\n" +
        "The quality of posts and views is an essential factor that creates the opinion of the social network about you and the thought of your potential subscribers, whose number will only increase over time due to the large number of materials viewed. Our service offers you to reach the top views on Instagram at no extra cost.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Why to buy ig views?",
    answer: "The presence of high-quality materials in the Instagram account is one of the most important criteria for the high-quality promotion. Another factor is the presence of many views, which arouses the interest of the audience in your content. First, you need to understand what status you currently belong to and what will give you the most efficiency:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Entrepreneurs:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Rapid growth in sales and recognition;\n" +
        "You will have a high level of trust;\n" +
        "If you are a novice entrepreneur, then for you this method of promotion is an excellent start for the development of activities;\n" +
        "For bloggers:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Immediate and rapid growth in the popularity of your account;\n" +
        "You can start earning from advertising;\n" +
        "The number of subscribers and activity is increasing;\n" +
        "Personal users:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Cheating Instagram followers as a quick increase in popularity;\n" +
        "Opportunity to earn;\n" +
        "If you are single, Instagram views will make you more popular; it will be easier for you to find your other half.\n" +
        "An important factor is the correct use of hashtags, which can also bring you to the TOP in views on Instagram.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy views on Instagram?",
    answer: "The most effective and high-quality ways to advertise on Instagram are paid methods. You save a significant amount of your time and achieve your goals faster.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The like insta resource allows you to use paid features:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "To get Instagram views , you should go to our website;\n" +
        "Next, you need to specify your hiring user and provide an email address;\n" +
        "Pay for the task in any convenient way. After a few minutes, the funds will be already in the account, and views will be added to your photos or videos in 5-15 minutes.\n" +
        "You can also buy ig video views cheaply and make your page promotion as easy and convenient as possible. Affordable pricing plans do not hit your advertising budget, which allows you to allocate financial resources rationally while getting a guaranteed result.",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Why choose Maketop to buy Instagram views?",
    answer: "The Maketop service will allow your publications to reach the top of Instagram views and, compared to its competitors, has some advantages:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Innovative and very convenient design that allows even a beginner to understand all the intricacies of promotion;\n" +
        "Anonymity and security. Properly configured cheat views will go unnoticed. This site is regularly used by media personalities and famous companies, without worrying about their reputation and data safety;\n" +
        "You do not need to enter your data into our database;\n" +
        "Support service is working promptly to help you resolve any issue related to the opration of the service;\n" +
        "Regular updates and unique developments. The service does not stand still and constantly monitors new algorithms for the operation of social networks. Thanks to this, you can get views on Instagram as quickly as possible;\n" +
        "Favorable and fair prices. You will spend a small part of your financial resources on promotion and get the best quality;\n" +
        "The service works around the clock, which allows us to cheat views without stopping, 24 hours a day.\n" +
        "You can endlessly list all the benefits of the service, but only the personal experience can give an objective assessment. Familiarize yourself with the convenient functionality and you, having spent only a few minutes of your time registering on the site.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We work with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, Discover, and you may even buy Instagram views with crypto.",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Who will benefit from views on Instagram for a fee?",
    answer: "Many people are skeptical about the artificial increase in views, that in their particular case, this method will not work. It is simply necessary for almost everyone:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "People who develop their accounts to gain popularity on Instagram. You only need to buy views on Instagram for videos or other materials.\n" +
        "Owners and administrators of various organizations have a tough time getting the right amount of traffic to their accounts due to narrow specialization.\n" +
        "Promotion by this method is vital for those who decide to run their private business on Instagram, because very often, published materials do not gain the proper amount of traffic, which is why there are no sales of goods or services.\n" +
        "To reach the TOP of Instagram, you need to artificially attract views to all publications at once since this factor directly affects the place in the network rating of your content;\n" +
        "Even if you only want to increase the activity on your page, then cheating views will be the most effective way to promote.",
    index: 5
  }
];

export const instagramCommentsQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy Instagram comments?",
    answer: "Buy cheap comments of the highest quality for your photos and videos here.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Comments are a profound aspect of account development. Thanks to them, people can communicate with each other and trust the user more because they see that his content resonates with the audience. Why is it worth buying custom Instagram comments on our service?\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The reasons:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "They can increase popularization since, in most cases, the audience leaves comments about a particular publication in the comments. For example, if a product is supplied they write whether it is good or bad, whether it matches the description, etc. The number of comments determines whether the account will be attractive to other people.\n" +
        "Thanks to the comments, the user will be able to earn the trust of people visiting his page for the first time to interest them. If he responds to other people's comments, it makes clear that he is a real person doing business or representing a company.\n" +
        "Comments are not just communication between users but also a good advertisement. If people see positive reviews about a product or service, they will often return to it and recommend it to their friends.\n" +
        "Comments help support communication with customers.\n" +
        "By conducting regular and sufficient work with comments, you can ensure a decent increase in likes and subscribers, which will allow your account to develop quickly and fruitfully.\n" +
        "The variety of content directly determines whether they will subscribe to the account. Comments dilute the materials provided on the page, and you can also post the most engaging and positive of them, thereby attracting new people.\n" +
        "As we have already found out, buying comments on Instagram means ensuring active communication between followers and allowing your account to develop quickly and increase its popularity.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What could be easier?",
    answer: "It is impossible to write comments on your own. You can't create many profiles. Moreover, they will be empty, and there is no point in using them. There is another way to hire people, but it will be expensive, and the comments will be copied from the network. Agree, an unattractive idea.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "However, there is a third way to wind up comments on Instagram. We will provide you with direct assistance in this at a symbolic price. You can create an active conversation under a personal photo or a picture of products, thus supplying visibility of the popularity of products.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It is worth noting that comments must meet several requirements to look the most authentic:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Use different active profiles. They must be real (with photographs, publications, etc.).\n" +
        "Instagram comment boost shouldn't be filled with overly positive reviews. It will cause suspicion not only to you but also to the product itself. If it is so popular, there must be at least one negative review?\n" +
        "It is impossible that the publication of comments was too frequent. It will also raise suspicion of falsification.\n" +
        "Services for boosting comments on Instagram often use dishonest methods: comments are monotonous, profiles are unrealistic, and the cost is crazy.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Buy real Instagram comments",
    answer: "The audience is not always active because it is easier for people to like it than typing tons of letters. Lack of activity affects the account popularity, which has a detrimental effect on the user's mood. If you buy comments on Instagram, a lot of opportunities open up:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The demand for content that is posted to the account is increasing;\n" +
        "Goods, services, or brands are advertised effectively; they begin to interest subscribers and make them turn to the user;\n" +
        "There is an opportunity to win the competition;\n" +
        "The attention of a large audience that shares a person's hobby is attracted;\n" +
        "An increase in subscribers is guaranteed.\n" +
        "Also, getting Instagram comments means organizing additional income for you, which will be received from a promoted account. Quite a lot of people are actively earning from advertising. To do this, you only need a popular and attractive page which will have a large number of active subscribers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We offer you quality Instagram comments in our store. Because our comments are from real people, they will help you properly promote your profile. By purchasing comments on our site, you can be sure that your account will not be blocked and photos will not be deleted!\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Our actions are fully compatible with the Instagram algorithm. You can get comments on Instagram quickly and easily. Hundreds of satisfied customers confirm the reliability and quality of our services. If you care about popularity and your account is still not number one on Instagram. It is time to take advantage of our offer.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We are working with different payment services, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy Instagram comments with crypto.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You can only buy Instagram live comments from SSL-certified websites with complete company information, details, services, and a price list.",
    index: 3
  }
];

export const freeInstagramLikesQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you get free Instagram likes?",
    answer: "Get free likes of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your account popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Do you have a trendy girlfriend in real life or on the Internet? Perhaps you have a friend who is easy to gain interest in yourself?! Of course, you have often wanted to be in the place of such a person? Well, it's easy. You need to take the first few steps. First of all, you need to wind up Instagram likes; this can be done for free using the service.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It is available to everyone, but not every person will believe in the effectiveness of such a resource. It is not a program and indeed not a robot, but an opportunity to increase your account's number of real followers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Work in the service can be performed not only from stationary computers but also from mobile devices. While studying, in the supermarket, in transport, or just for a walk, you can get Instagram likes for free.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "In addition, our company involves cheating subscribers and comments on the most popular social networks on the Internet. And even if you still don't have a personal page on Instagram, you can use the service's capabilities on other portals designed for communication and information exchange.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "How to get more Instagram likes for free?",
    answer: "To increase the popularity of your photos on Instagram, I recommend using the basic rules:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Take YOUR high-quality and exciting photos. Do not post other people's pictures on the Internet; they are of no interest to anyone.\n" +
        "If you didn't get caught by a photo, then hook it with a description to give you a heart or write a comment. Communicate with the audience through the description, ask them questions, and provoke them to leave a comment. Thus, the post can attract even more attention and likes.\n" +
        "Put the hashtags correctly.\n" +
        "Make your profile public and design it well. Put a beautiful profile picture and tell us who you are or what you do.\n" +
        "Like, follow, and comment on other accounts to get reciprocal action.\n" +
        "Try to post more often, but not too often. At least one or two a day.\n" +
        "Make geolocation tags where the photo was taken. You can also go to the top and attract attention.\n" +
        "Those who want to save their own money and understand the Instagram ranking mechanisms will be interested to learn how to get free Instagram likes . To do this, you can use various methods; here are the main working methods:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Hashtags and geotags\n" +
        "Choose suitable tags for each post; add information about the geolocation when placing your publications. The system allows you to specify up to 30 hashtags; it is better to limit yourself to 10 Instagram likes free trials to not reload your post and make it look attractive. You can add 4-5 popular tags to your posts and cover the mid-and low-frequency tags in the other half. It will also be helpful to come up with your hashtag and add it to each post.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Manual mass liking\n" +
        "Be active, put hearts even to strangers, they will probably reciprocate. Despite the apparent simplicity of this method, one should not count on one hundred percent return. Not many users today use this method to get free Instagram likes 2022 - it takes a lot of time; the network sets limits on actions, and not everyone wants to count the number of hearts left.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Software mass liking\n" +
        "Programs and applications allow you to leave hearts on behalf of your account automatically. This is, of course, much faster and easier than liking user posts on your own. But this method has significant drawbacks: the ability to download a virus along with the program, lose access to your account, and get blocked for exceeding the limits. Of course, there are also worthy software representatives, but access to such tools is usually paid.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Exchanges - exchangers\n" +
        "This method can help you get likes on Instagram from scratch on your own, and it is much more effective than regular mass liking. By registering on the exchanges, you are sure that your like-minded people live there. But the essence is the same - you perform actions and receive a reward. Then you create your task and pay for the work of the performers. It turns out that, in this case, you will again need a long period of time to get the required number of likes.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Is it safe to buy likes?",
    answer: "Cheat likes on Instagram are absolutely safe if you use them wisely. We do not share your data: be calm about your privacy! Your account will not be hacked or stolen!\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Do not get carried away with cheating if you have few followers on your profile. It is essential to maintain a balance: the number of hearts should not exceed 30% of the number of subscribers. If you have 1 thousand subscribers and 900 likes, this will raise questions from users. This discrepancy can cause distrust in your audience, as well as in the Instagram system itself.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "A social network can restrict your actions or even block your account for excessive suspicious activity. However, you have nothing to fear if you act carefully and do not wind up millions of hearts at once.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You are getting:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "fast winding speed;\n" +
        "quality likes;\n" +
        "convenient site interface;\n" +
        "bonus system;\n" +
        "detailed statistics.\n" +
        "With us, you can not worry about the security of your data and access to the page. Cheat is fast, safe, and easy!",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "What gives likes on Instagram?",
    answer: "Boosting likes on Instagram allows you to draw attention to your profile. Many likes signal to other users that your services and products are attractive. Recently, people put their hearts in less and less, and therefore their presence signals genuine interest in the post. If your posts have a lot of likes, we can be sure that users are not afraid to become your client or subscriber.",
    index: 4
  }
];

export const freeInstagramFollowersQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you get 10 Free Instagram Followers?",
    answer: "Buy followers of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your channel popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Instagram is one of the largest social networks, with 800 million monthly active users. This can work wonders for your business, but to make money on Instagram, you need to optimize your account first (just like you need to optimize your website for Google).",
    index: 1
  },
  {
      question: "Buying Instagram Followers: Choosing the Benefits",
      answer: "You can collect networks in different ways, but judging by the number of users, many resources for modern people cannot be underestimated if you want to wind up followers on Instagram. Moreover, many Internet users no longer think of their person without their favorite \"social networks\" and balance with a balanced morning cup of coffee. They start their day by checking pages for new comments and exciting entries in the feed.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Experts identify several main reasons associated with owners who resort to paid cheating of people's followers on Instagram. First of all, this requires increasing the authority of your account because the presence of a large number of followers on Instagram automatically means that this blog contains interesting information worthy of attention.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "It doesn't matter if the rapid growth of the number of followers on Instagram is accompanied by your desire to realize personal ambitions or the desire to promote a business account. When you have natural resources and Instagram followers in large numbers, it makes a profit!\n" +
          "\n" +
          "The probability of appearing in the blogosphere is incredibly high; solving the problem with access to Instagram followers is more likely and faster than followers. Even if your pictures are exciting and unusual, getting 1000 followers on Instagram is naturally time-consuming because it is simply impressive for any smaller number of accounts, and it is very difficult for beginners.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "It was decided to wind up followers on Instagram online by choosing to upgrade your page and high positions in the ranking quickly. For example, cheating followers on Instagram using our website allows you to multiply the number of your followers in a few days!\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Artificially cheating followers on Instagram means that external visitors of social networks begin to pay attention to your photoblog and visit it! When an account reaches the TOP, it immediately becomes popular and arouses interest among users. Thus, Instagram followers earn money for you and free followers because the well-known stereotype from the category \"where everyone is, there I am\" works here. Put, when a person notices that you have a lot of followers on Instagram, they will probably want to follow or at least bookmark your page to explore it more gradually in the future. It is challenging for most social media users to pay attention to those who have 1000 followers on Instagram or many times more, and new subscriptions cover further promotion of the account and growth in popularity!",
      index: 2
  },
  {
      question: "Cheat live followers on Instagram for the implementation of commercial goals and objectives",
      answer: "Getting followers on Instagram online will become a relevant solution for promoting business projects on social networks, regardless of whether we are talking about information products or ordinary goods or services. The Internet has long been an essential tool for communicating with customers, and the leading social network is no exception to the rule.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Not everyone considers it worth buying Instagram followers to show off new vacation photos taken at a prestigious resort or buying a foreign status car. Although on the other hand, why not take the celebrity example, whose life we have the opportunity to observe through personal photo blogs?\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Own Instagram accounts, regularly updated with new pictures, are now available not only for show business stars who, due to the specifics of their work, love publicity but also for politicians, athletes, and other people with serious professions.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Of course, each person himself sets the boundaries of personal space and decides whether it is worth informing the whole world about his personal life. But even the most notorious skeptics are unlikely to doubt that live Instagram followers, which you can buy on the pages of our resource, will be able to make up an active part of your consumer audience. They can bring considerable profit if you use social network resources to promote products and services!\n" +
          "\n" +
          "The more people know about your product, the more orders you can get, so ignoring building a large subscription base is giving your profits to competitors!\n" +
          "\n" +
          "It would help if you did not discount the fact that Instagram followers for a fee help increase loyalty to your product from ordinary social network users. If an account has a lot of followers, this is clear evidence that the product is in demand.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Hundreds of thousands of people around the world regularly make sales through their Instagram accounts, and many solid commercial projects began their existence from social resources. First, you invest in buying live followers on Instagram. In return, you get a positive reputation and the trust of potential customers, for whom a large number of followers on your account automatically means that the product you offer is excellent and valuable for the buyer.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "In addition, the presence of a large subscriber base allows you to quickly inform them about your company's new offers by sending relevant notifications to e-mail so that any advertising will become much more effective.",
      index: 3
  },
  {
      question: "Definition of the target audience",
      answer: "One of the decisive factors is correctly defined target audience. If you misidentify, you will only be wasting your money trying to attract people who don't care or need your services or products. There is a traditional way to help you with this. It would help if you answered the following questions:\n" +
          "\n" +
          "What is the average age of your audience?\n" +
          "Where do these people live?\n" +
          "Do they have a job? What job?\n" +
          "Are they active on Instagram?",
      index: 4
  },
  {
      question: "How to Get Your First free Instagram followers: Basic Optimization",
      answer: "Let's assume that you have completed all the previous points and the preparatory work is done. Now is the time to think about optimizing your account. Here are a few steps to help you.",
      index: 5
  },
  {
      question: "Filling in information about yourself and creating a profile",
      answer: "The \"face\" of your account comes first. Your name, header, links, and all the necessary information. Let's take a closer look at what you need to have here.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Let's start with the account name. It should not exceed 30 characters and preferably include a keyword. Next is your username. It should match the one you use on other social networks, and then it will not be difficult for your subscribers to find your accounts.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "The header bio, as mentioned earlier, should be as informative as the 150 characters allowed. Any new visitor should be able to understand what he is dealing with instantly. And don't forget to include your website link in your profile header!",
      index: 6
  },
  {
      question: "Maintain consistency in content and create your own style on Instagram",
      answer: "The overall look of your account is also of great importance. The style of the brand itself should be very clearly traced. All content must be published in the same manner, without apparent differences from other posts. It is best to create a unique design that will make you stand out from other companies.",
      index: 7
  },
  {
      question: "How to get your 10 Instagram followers free trial: Content",
      answer: "Content is a significant part of your subscriber acquisition plan. Think for yourself: if the content in your account is not interesting or does not attract users, then why should they follow you? We will look at the basic rules for creating content and give some recommendations for optimizing it.",
      index: 8
  },
  {
      question: "Use popular and relevant hashtags",
      answer: "Hashtags are one of the most important parts of promoting your personal brand. They allow people who aren't following you to contact you when they're looking for a specific destination or product. If you use this tool wisely, it can lead to an increase in the number of your subscribers. Let's see how to use it:\n" +
          "\n" +
          "First, you need to know what hashtags you can use and which will bring the desired results. Find out what hashtags other companies in your industry are using. You can evaluate the effectiveness of hashtags using unique services such as Mention.com.\n" +
          "Please don't get carried away too much. If you add a hundred hashtags under every post, it will only seem out of place and completely unconvincing. Even worse, it will look like spam. You definitely wouldn't want that.\n" +
          "Trying to fool everyone with dishonest techniques such as \"mutual likes\" and the like will only create problems for yourself. Using these hashtags will gain a certain number of new followers; however, they will not be interested in your services or those of your company. Their only goal will be to collect likes and reposts, that's all.\n" +
          "Last but not least, stories. An insanely powerful and up-to-date tool that allows millions of people to view unique content. Hashtags also work in conjunction with levels. Add them to your accounts to avoid missing a single potential client.",
      index: 9
  },
  {
      question: "Cheat followers on Instagram online to participate in contests",
      answer: "Instagram positions itself as a social network for young and active people, so online Instagram followers will come in handy for those who want to be not just a passive contemplator but take an active part in a life resource.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "First of all, we are talking about mass contests, which become much easier if you buy followers on Instagram and enlist their support in voting. Contests on Instagram are observed; participation in these events is a great way to express yourself and close valuable prizes from the organizers.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "A reasonably suitable tariff plan on our website and cheating-free Instagram followers 2022 allows you to maximize the number of likes for your photos! Quite often, the winner of any contest is the one with the most likes, and this is possible with a large number of followers. Cheating among followers on Instagram is individual, like cheating likes is problematic, so it's best to buy a suitable Smmlaba service package and watch the maximum number of followers every day.",
      index: 10
  },
  {
      question: "Paid promotion methods",
      answer: "Targeted advertising\n" +
          "Official Instagram advertising is an opportunity to reach an audience with specific interests. If the algorithms themselves decide who to show your Reels or post to, then in advertising, you set the audience yourself. Instagram offers to advertise in the feed, stories, and Reels.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Advertising is configured on Instagram itself or through the Facebook advertising account (if the account is linked to the page). For advertising on Instagram, goals are available: visiting an account, a website, and increasing engagement - more messages. The audience can be selected automatically or configured, but the criteria are limited.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "The disadvantage of social network advertising is an impressive list of constantly changing restrictions. Advertising is stopped for violation of the rules, and sometimes the account is blocked without explanation.\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Advertising with influencers\n" +
          "Influence marketing remains trending in 2022 as the blogging market grows. Therefore, Instagram promotion through opinion leaders is still relevant. Advertising among bloggers, famous personalities, and experts is more trustworthy and is perceived as a recommendation of a familiar person—advertising options for influencers: native (does not look like advertising) or direct.",
      index: 11
  }
];

export const youtubeViewsQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy YouTube Views?",
    answer: "Buy views of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your channel popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "YouTube is an Internet platform created in the USA and allows users to upload their videos and watch others' videos, leave comments, rate, subscribe to channels, and share videos with friends on various sites and social networks.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The range is considerably differs from entertaining to earning opportunities. And for some, maintaining a channel brings money. In addition, you can run and listen to broadcasts in real-time.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Each person uploads ~30,000 videos;\n" +
        "Every day people watch 1 billion hours of video;\n" +
        "90% of TV shows are people aged 18 to 44.\n" +
        "The first video, which lasted 18 seconds, marked the beginning of the future and is now a very famous YouTube platform. In two months, starting from scratch, he gained a stable position on the Internet. Work on YouTube continues and is still improving the functionality of the platform.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Watching free videos is provided by the company. These expenses are repaid by it through advertising. The introduction of advertising was carried out by the company's management in 2008. The three students, who were at the head of YouTube, were replaced by Kamangar, with the help of which YouTube was taken to a new level.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "An interesting fact is no one could think of creating a service where you can use free videos before students - programmers. It is a pity that they are not now in charge of it. Registration for the benefit is complimentary for all users. To register your profile, you need to have an email on Google.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "After that, you can access all YouTube services. You can manage your channel, leave comments, and add videos. It is not allowed to post material on the platform that intimidates the user, such as a pornographic videotape; a plot that humiliates a child; shocking videos, discriminatory, inciting to dangerous actions, spam, and videos with a prohibition of use.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Buy views on Youtube",
    answer: "More than 1 billion users visit YouTube every month. Their goals are different, but they do not stop being potential customers or subscribers. But do they see you, your company, your idea, your product? It depends on many factors. And the number of video views is one of the main ones. That is why the « get 1000 youtube views\" service is so prevalent on our service. Bright and spectacular videotapes, shot with taste, invariably attract the attention of thousands of users, winding up views one after another.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Watching YouTube in 2021-2022 remains one of the most popular ways to spend time. YouTube promotion is growing exponentially and helps to achieve goals. But getting into the rating without an absolute sensation is not easy.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "How to be the first in Youtube search results?",
    answer: "If your channel is not popular enough and you want to attract a new target audience, then upload a video clip, think over the key queries you need promotion. Indicate them in tags, and write a unique description for the video using the main queries you need to promote.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Immediately after downloading, buy YouTube views, likes, dislikes, reposts, and comments. Buying subscribers on YouTube - the popularity of the video at the start will immediately push it as high as possible in the search results ranking for promoted queries, after which you will receive thousands of targeted views from real users.",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Live, real views with YouTube hold",
    answer: "What is YouTube Hold Views? Retention is a measure of audience engagement while protecting your tape. The higher the view retention, the easier it is to promote the video, bring it to the top for keywords, and get into the recommended videos.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "YouTube views with retention will help you quickly and easily promote any video and make it viral, bring it to the TOP of search, and get youtube views from real users who found your video in YouTube search or Yandex and Google search. You can buy YouTube views with retention of 10 minutes or more right now from live, real users. YouTube views cheat 2021-2022 will help to increase your audience exponentially.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Cheat views on YouTube are your choice if:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You stand looking to make \"quick\" sales.\n" +
        "Your goal is TOP places in YouTube ratings.\n" +
        "It is in your interest to present a product or service to the mark audience quickly.\n" +
        "You are trying to reach a large number of users.\n" +
        "You want to attract advertisers from the business environment.",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy YouTube views?",
    answer: "Modern social networks and Internet platforms open up endless possibilities for users regarding the search for information, communication, and earnings. YouTube is a unique Internet platform of its kind, where each user can freely express thoughts, ideas and develop their own business, projects, and directions.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Many successful people and businesses in the market owe their success to YouTube. The platform works as simply and clearly, as possible - users upload new videos to their channel, which gain tens, hundreds, thousands, or millions of sights.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Thus, channel owners increase the number of visitors to their own sites and expand the number of charges, hence the amount of profit. At the same time, every second channel owner thinks about how to improve views on YouTube, YouTube favorites, and the channel's popularity.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "By becoming a client of our service, you can be convinced of its effectiveness. A completely new channel or a channel that has not been working effectively for a long time will be able to get cheap YouTube views.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy YouTube views with crypto.",
    index: 5
  }
];

export const youtubeLikesQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy YouTube likes?",
    answer: "Buy here real likes of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your channel popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "On the YouTube video hosting service, factors such as the number of subscribers, video views, and likes put on them are involved in the development of the channel. No wonder the authors of the channels ask you to press the coveted “thumbs up” after watching the video. It helps to promote the channel up to the top positions.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Like is a reflection of the level of sympathy that the audience experiences regarding a particular video and, in general, regarding the work of the author on the channel.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Why do likes have such a strong influence on channel promotion? It is a live activity of the audience, accelerating the output of the video to the top of YouTube and Google searches. Automated systems read the information that a liked video is reasonable for users.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "On YouTube, the intra-system principle of promoting videos also works if the other owner of the channel has a playlist \"Like Videos\". It displays all the videos that have been liked and mean that users subscribed to this person will also see it.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Likes on YouTube. What bonuses does the author receive from them?",
    answer: "Why to buy YouTube custom likes? Here are the bonuses:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "the loyalty of the audience to the channel, periodically uploaded videos to it, and the personality of the author as a whole (or to the promoted brand) is formed;\n" +
        "the audience is filled with new subscribers who see the interest of other people;\n" +
        "the video is moving to the top.\n" +
        "Popularization of the channel logically leads to encouragement from the YouTube platform itself. There is an opportunity to advertise goods and services and work in this direction under different conditions. Viewers from the YouTube channel become subscribers to other social networks of the author and provide opportunities to increase earnings.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy YouTube likes?",
    answer: "The algorithm of actions on the site to buy likes on YouTube:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "To get YouTube likes explore all packages in the Likes category and choose the one that suits your offer and its price. Consider this choice carefully if you have not worked with Maketop before. Click on the service icon to read the information.\n" +
        "Click on the \"Order\" button if you have replenished your wallet on the site.\n" +
        "After filling in all the lines, it remains only to wait for the queue for its execution by the service.\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy YouTube likes with crypto.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The specificity of the Maketop service is to automate its work. Each client can use the services of interest at any time. At the same time, there is the round-the-clock technical support that answers user questions. The client pays for his order and gets in line. The terms of execution and the daily volume are specified in the information for the order, so you should not worry about a long wait.",
    index: 3
  }
];

export const youtubeCommentsQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy YouTube comments?",
    answer: "Buy comments of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your channel popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "YouTube is a video hosting service that is well known and popular all over the world. Maintaining a channel on this Internet resource is rightfully considered one of the most effective tools for promoting your brand, business, goods, services, and name. YouTube allows each user to become famous, successful, wealthy, and achieve unprecedented heights in video blogging or other areas.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Increasing the popularity by boosting YouTube comments is an effective marketing tool for private video bloggers or companies that want to quickly draw attention to their products with the help of thematic videos.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Creating and posting videos is one of the best ways to promote products and services online. The proverb that it is better to see once than to hear many times remains relevant; due to high competition, the promotion of any channel requires a considerable amount of time.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "By deciding to buy YouTube custom comments, you will significantly increase the effectiveness of your advertising campaign and quickly get your first profit.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The number of views of the video increases many times, which causes increased interest in it from potential viewers. Seeing many subscriptions, comments, and likes, other users will probably want to subscribe to your channel or take part in a discussion that has aroused great interest.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Channel creators are trying to attract attention with their channels. At Maketop, we want to help you get the most out of YouTube. For that, we have a lot of valuable tips and quality YouTube comment suggestions.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Why to buy comments?",
    answer: "Boosting comments on YouTube content is your decision if:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You need \"quick\" deals.\n" +
        "Your goal is to interact with the audience and get feedback.\n" +
        "Your mission is to make a favorable impression and keep a reputation.\n" +
        "The channel rating and audience action are essential to you.\n" +
        "You're aiming for YouTube rankings.\n" +
        "It is in your interest to thoroughly and quickly present a product or service to the target audience.\n" +
        "You need to achieve the maximum allowed number of viewers.\n" +
        "Your preference is YouTube promotion.\n" +
        "You desire to entice advertisers from the business environment.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy YouTube comments?",
    answer: "We offer to buy effective and safe methods to increase user activity and the number of subscribers on YouTube channels. When buying comments on our YouTube service, comments are done by real people from different devices, so the discussion looks completely natural.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Comments are written in accordance with the cheating task you bought. You can choose performers according to the criteria you are interested in, including gender, age, and region of residence. This option combines efficiency and affordable cost.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We provide only the highest quality services. No compromises - only the best promotion for our clients.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Incredibly high-speed YouTube comments will allow you to get excellent promotions in the shortest possible time.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "As for the content of the posts that you buy with the service, you can offer your posts or create a task, the requirements of which will guide the offers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You can become our client and get YouTube comments at any convenient time. Fill out the application form on the site indicating your requirements and the cost of one comment.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy YouTube comments with crypto.",
    index: 3
  }
];

export const tiktokLikesQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy TikTok likes?",
    answer: "Buy likes of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your channel popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "What is TikTok? In fact, it is the quintessence of Vine, Instagram Stories, Snapchat, and other services focused on the short video format. On TikTok, users post small 15 seconds long vertical videos and get millions of views. They are music videos, comedy sketches, dances, reactions to trends, and other activities.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Many consider this social network to be just another entertainment for teenagers, where they grimace at the camera and hold various flash mobs. It is partly true, but with the growth of the platform's audience, celebrities and advertisers have become interested in it, and well-known bloggers now regard TikTok as another distribution channel.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Why is TikTok so popular?",
    answer: "Initially, the Chinese application was a service for editing and publishing short videos to which you could add music. The social network gained popularity outside of China after the takeover of the musical.ly app, similar in function, whose large user base automatically became the TikTok audience. TikTok has become popular in Canada, the USA, the UK, and Malaysia.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "TikTok carved out a mini-video niche by capturing the audience of the closed Vine and taking a share of Instagram* Stories. The format of short videos with rich editing options, as they say, shot. For example, in the United States at the end of 2018, the social network surpassed such giants as Facebook, YouTube, and Instagram in terms of the number of downloads.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "How to use TikTok?",
    answer: "The platform is very similar to its counterparts, and if you've ever used Snapchat or Instagram Stories, then it's not difficult to figure out the functionality. However, there are still some differences and nuances in TikTok.",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Ways to promote",
    answer: "TikTok, like many other social networks, has an advertising account called TikTok Ads. It offers several official ways to advertise:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "TopView - banners that the user sees when entering the social network;\n" +
        "Brand Takeover - short videos that the user sees periodically;\n" +
        "In-Feed Ads - native ads that pop up in the feed;\n" +
        "Branded Effects - promotion using augmented reality: masks, stickers;\n" +
        "Branded Hashtag Challenge - branded challenges.\n" +
        "However, a business can use other tools to work on TikTok, for example, collaborations with bloggers. Or a company can create an account and shoot videos regularly. It is better if they are original and slightly frivolous. The chances of success increase when the videos follow the trends and include popular hashtags.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Making videos for TikTok is not as easy as it sounds. One creative will not be enough: you will have to develop a full-fledged promotion strategy. It should determine in advance the goals and objectives, characteristics of the target audience, key performance indicators, and their desired values.",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "And who can't do without TikTok?",
    answer: "But still, TikTok is best suited for small and medium-sized businesses that work with retail clients - these are the companies that are the easiest to find the right audience there. In addition, small and medium-sized businesses have to work with limited budgets, and promotion on TikTok cannot be very expensive - if, of course, company employees have creative ideas and enough free time.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "If we talk about areas, then videos on the topics of creativity, cooking, fashion, beauty, and personal care are most organically watched on TikTok - such videos are generally in demand on the platform. It is largely due to the gender composition of the audience: 54% of app users are women.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Getting likes on TikTok is the fastest, most efficient, and most effective method to increase the chances of getting into recommendations and promoting your account. Millions will know about you! Take advantage of this. A large number of likes and views affect your further promotion and promotion.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "TOP tiktokers do not hesitate to order a cheat on their new videos that is why you notice them so often in your feed. Getting likes on TikTok and fans directly affects your reputation in the TikTok project, post new posts; order likes, and gets explosive, increased audience coverage! You can buy likes on TikTok right now, on our website from real people quickly and easily!\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Many celebrities of TOP social networks have successfully started their careers using our service. How to wind up TikTok? Why do we need TikTok likes 2021-2022?\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Buying likes on TikTok is the easiest, safest, fastest, and most effective way to promote your account to increase its popularity. Stand out from the general stream and become famous at lightning speed, take TOP places in the ranking. Account owners with a large number of likes and fans have the opportunity to earn on advertising. The more likes and fans, the more expensive it is. Take advantage of this opportunity!",
    index: 5
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy TikTok likes- who needs it and why?",
    answer: "TikTok likes are an indicator of video popularity. They allow videos to be more noticeable and largely determine the attitude of other users to your profile and video content. In social networks, the rule works perfectly: where everyone is, there I am. Viewers enjoy watching videos that have already received thousands of likes from other users. At the same time, videos with a small number of views and likes rarely attract the attention of the audience.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Likes TikTok and TikTok views are like vitamins for the body. Without them, the profile will cease to perform its functions and eventually die. At the same time, many likes will allow the account to develop and flourish, to bring \"fruits\" in the form of growing income to its owner.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Boosting likes on TikTok will help to attract the attention of:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "a wide audience of users;\n" +
        "advertisers;\n" +
        "the social network itself, which with great pleasure independently advertises a video that has received a lot of likes.\n" +
        "A promoted TikTok account will allow you to earn good money on advertising. The popularity of an account is determined not only by the number of followers but also by the number of likes. A profile that has 10,000 followers but 3-5 likes on a video is unlikely to attract an advertiser's attention. A comprehensive promotion is required - cheating on TikTok likes and subscribers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Who get likes on a TikTok video:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "bloggers;\n" +
        "owners of a small, medium, and large businesses;\n" +
        "entrepreneurial people who want to make money on advertising;\n" +
        "ambitious users who want to promote their project or their name.\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may evenbuy TikTok likes with crypto.",
    index: 6
  }
];

export const tiktokViewsQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy TikTok views?",
    answer: "Buy real views of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and evolve famous.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "TikTok is one of the most famous social networks today. Like Instagram or Facebook, it allows you to share short videos with other people. Today, almost all teenagers worldwide use this site to present their videos and communicate with each other.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Why do you need a TikTok account?",
    answer: "TikTok belongs to the new social networks, but it has already gained many fans. There are around 800 million users worldwide, and it is easy to predict that its popularity will continue to increase.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Today, promoting your brand or yourself requires a presence on social media. People who follow profiles on Facebook, Instagram, and now on TikTok is extremely effective here. That's why you should take the possibility to purchase views and followers. It will make your videos recorded on TikTok much more popular. Ticket impressions are also a guarantee of lucrative contracts with advertisers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "If you determine to get TikTok views , then they will be increased under your videos; you can be certain that many people will see the content you share. After that, when they start tracking your profile, your growth is only a matter of time. If you want to earn recognition in TikTok, you must take the opportunity to purchase views. Our assistance will save you time and provide quality traffic to your profile. When you get views on Maketop, you choose the high rate and mega popularity online.\n" +
        "\n",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Is it secure to buy views in Tik Tok?",
    answer: "It is 100% safe for your TikTok account, as we operate with real profiles that make your profile known and secure. It is a guarantee of quality services. So do you want to be covered quickly and safely in the media? Maketop will do it professionally and confidently!",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy TikTok views?",
    answer: "When creating a rating on TikTok, several factors are taken into account, one of which is the number of views. TikTok has millions of active users a month! It means, that if you want to stand out, you will require making an effort. Buying views in TikTok will let you optimize your range and give it the impetus for development needed to stay ahead of the competition.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We suggest high-quality video cheating on the market at affordable prices and have been providing TikTok users with high-quality and unique views for many years. Entrust your video rating to a respected provider of social marketing and PR benefits\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You need to:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "select any TikTok package and click Order\n" +
        "specify your email address;\n" +
        "choose a payment option.\n" +
        "We are working with different payment services, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy TikTok views with crypto.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We use some of the biggest names in hip-hop, sports, and television. Building strong relationships and providing high-quality customer service, we stand out from the competition.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Our patented system provides you with access to the views you want without compromising the integrity of your account or video.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "By buying more views for your videos, you gain great authority in the eyes of TikTok, search engines, and your colleagues. Let's face it: no one wants to watch a video that has very few views.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We offer round-the-clock support and a convenient toolbar to track your progress!",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Why do people buy Tik Tok views in Stream Promotion?",
    answer: "Many people use our services. Why? It's simple - a group of professionals provides services at a lower price and fast processing of orders.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Maketop has many satisfied customers who recommend us to their friends. It is a trustworthy service. Therefore, if your videos do not yet have the required quantity of views, choose one of the options, add it to your demands and reach a high position on TikTok.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Streaming is a 100% real and reliable site for buying all kinds of cheating social networks. The service never requires confidential information such as profile passwords and personal data. All this makes you 100% secure.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The most desirable advantage is cost reduction and high quality of service, which is the motto of our work. Another advantage of our followers is that we provide safe and trustworthy assistance with real human followers on all social networks.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "There is no need to bother about your purchased views disappearing over time. The accounts that will ensure your success on TikTok are genuine and will stay with your subscribers. Your videos will always be high attendance. Your subscribers are real users, and they can also subscribe to your posts and videos on Instagram or Facebook.",
    index: 5
  }
];

export const twitterFollowersQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy Twitter Followers?",
    answer: "Buy followers of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your account popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "What is Twitter? Here begins the most interesting, because in our opinion, most companies do not know what a tweeter is for and how to use it.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "To understand this, you need to know the features of the tweeter and how it differs from other social networks.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Twitter features:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Information on Twitter about past, ongoing and planned events spreads faster than on any Internet site or social network. The speed of information dissemination today is Twitter ~ 5 minutes, Tapes ~ 1 hour, Radio ~ 30 minutes, TV ~ 2 hours.\n" +
        "Twitter messages are available to all Twitter users, which is (as of January 1, 2011) over 200 million users! And this figure is growing at an unprecedented rate.\n" +
        "Twitter is trendy. In promoting their company, in public relations, the tweeter is used only by those companies that follow current trends and keep up with the times.\n" +
        "In this way, if you have a Twitter, you don't just follow some fashion, you can make your company, your product, or your message known instantly to millions of users.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "How is a Twitter set up?",
    answer: "Any registered Twitter user can send messages with a maximum of 140 characters. Messages can contain any information (opinions, news, ideas, and events) and links to site pages (articles, news, jokes, reasonable information). Links to videos and images (photos, pictures, jokes, music) are prevalent\n" +
        "\n" +
        "An essential parameter of the popularity of a particular tweeter user is the number of followers and the number of retweets of his tweeter.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Followers on Twitter are people who follow the messages of a particular tweeter user. If many followers follow your messages, it means that, what you write is interesting and valuable to them.\n" +
        "Retweet - repeating a message Retweet - repeating a message. Retweet allows you to repeat your message by clicking on the special Retweet button or by inserting the abbreviation RT before the quoted message.\n" +
        "If your message is quoted, then it is something interesting that should become known to others. The retweet system is a way to make a message known to friends (followers) and friends of friends.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Twitter is a unique social network. Unlike other countries in the world of portals, the scope limits the number of post users. Each post must be no more than 140 characters.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Despite this fact, it was Twitter that met frequently. With over 400 million visits every month, the social network is the perfect gathering place. On this occasion, such a service as cheating followers on Twitter caused a resonance.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "How does this mechanism work?",
    answer: "The subscriber cheat service is created on the operation of a simple psychological mechanism: we will always be interested in what is happening. That is, if you briefly describe everything, you get Twitter followers cheap:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The more subscribers a page has, the more it is viewed.\n" +
        "Users are more likely to be matched with an audience of many thousands or millions of people than for profiles whose number of subscribers disappears infrequently.\n" +
        "It turns out that the more subscribers you have the more of them you will have. Since it is simply impossible to compete with the top pages on your own, the obvious way out is the help of outside specialists.",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Cheat followers on Twitter",
    answer: "Why have Twitter accounts if there is no one to read it? Is there anyone but you do not know how to find them? Cheating Twitter subscribers will allow you to quickly and effectively increase the audience of readers. All you need to start the natural subscription process is to pick up attractive content and order a Twitter follower boost online.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Twitter Followers 2021-2022 significantly increases the share of your account compared to others. A simple and safe procedure from market experts will help you form a subscriber base, create a presentable account, and expand the reach of your target audience.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Our company has brought together the best specialists in the field of promotion to provide profitable solutions for online businesses. We use proven and reliable tools and achieve our goals!",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy Twitter followers without risk?",
    answer: "All social networks have a negative attitude towards any artificial increase in resources - cheating subscribers, likes, views, and comments. Twitter is no exception. The social network put forward a lot of requirements for activity in any account, among them the speed of cheating followers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Too high rate of subscribers can be perceived by Twitter as a threat to the security of other users and the social network itself. Violation of the established limits and requirements inevitably leads to retaliatory measures - restrictions or more global penalties.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "In order not to fall out of favor with robots that monitor anomalous activity in accounts, you should choose proven methods of promotion (such as following likes on Twitter) and reliable sites for promotion on social networks. Our platform guarantees the safe promotion of followers on Twitter.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We use the author's software and select an individual rate of resource cheating for each account. Our specialists closely monitor compliance with the requirements and norms of social networks to protect your pages from bans and other restrictions. The presence of an impressive contact base allows each client of the service to buy Twitter subscribers in large numbers, inexpensively, and without risks.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We provide only the highest quality services. No compromises - only the best promotion for our clients.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy Twitter followers with crypto.",
    index: 5
  }
];

export const twitterLikesQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where to buy Twitter likes?",
    answer: "Here you can buy real likes at reasonable prices and get the best help you need to be in trends.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Twitter is one of the most popular social networks in our world. A page in it is an excellent opportunity to promote your business, ideas, and creativity. Accounts in this network are created by all well-known companies, artists, and artists. In the Internet age, interaction with the audience reaches a new level.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "However, what's the point of tweets if no one sees them? How to attract the right audience?\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The answer is simple - promote the page. One of the elements of promotion is to get likes on posts.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Why do you need to get likes on Twitter?",
    answer: "First of all, getting likes on Twitter is needed so that potential customers or fans of creativity can find the page. As you know, pages with many followers, views, and likes rank higher in search engines.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "A new page always scares customers. They feel like they are deceived. At the same time, a page with many followers and likes is credible. People begin to think that the company has many satisfied regular customers, which means that the product or service is of high quality.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It is always challenging for a new page to compete with giant sisters. These pages have been growing in popularity for years, so how can you catch up and overtake them in a couple of days? The only option is to buy likes. In addition, when the page reaches the top, people will find it themselves and follow it.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Buying likes on Twitter will help to attract the target audience. Over time, this page will be seen by people who are interested in its content and looking for something similar. Our company winds up likes within the target group, with the right interests, the required age, and geographic location, and you get Twitter likes cheap.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Buying likes will help save on advertising. The page will promote itself. No additional advertising is needed, and therefore, this will help reduce costs. People who want to buy your product will find you.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Who needs to buy likes on Twitter?",
    answer: "Anyone who wants to promote a page on Twitter needs likes:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Entrepreneurs. First of all, it concerns business. Likes will allow the company page to reach the first lines in search engines, which increases the number of potential customers and, as a result, sales.\n" +
        "Artists, painters, poets. For creative people, likes will allow promoting your poems, paintings, and songs.\n" +
        "Social movements. A Twitter page can be created by social movements and organizations. It will help to find supporters and bring their thoughts to the masses.\n" +
        "Bloggers. In the modern Internet space, blogs are beginning to occupy an increasing place.",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy Twitter likes?",
    answer: "The promotion of Twitter by our specialists is an opportunity for new and existing accounts to become more popular and rise higher in the overall ranking. No special knowledge is needed - just select the desired service package, pay for it, and almost immediately see an increase in likes to tweets.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We have a lot of advantages:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "target orientation - likes are put from real users;\n" +
        "accessibility - you choose how many likes you need; and also plan your budget;\n" +
        "speed - the first likes appear immediately.\n" +
        "We work with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, and Discover, and you may even buy Twitter likes with crypto.",
    index: 4
  }
];

export const facebookPageLikesQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy Facebook Page Likes?",
    answer: "Buy real likes of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and make your account popular.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Social networks are open communication with the audience, a sound signal, a means of communication, and self-expression. Millions of users view posts and like the posts they enjoy.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Why Facebook?",
    answer: "Many of us are based not only on communication with people, we know by sight, communicate with people, make friends, but also to expand troubles, for example, those with which it is reasonable to communicate in the professional field, exchange experience, knowledge, and skills.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Facebook allows you to increase your circle of acquaintances and enter a professional environment with comfort and without special requirements. Colleagues and people who are interested in certain areas of professional activity, are dedicated to discussing issues related to the economy, finance, work, leisure, sports, and other fascinating topics within profiles and pages.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Facebook allows you to expand your horizons for business, create professional connections, start a pleasant conversation, and share your opinion on the issue under discussion. There is an unlimited number of topics for discussion within the page and profile. And this is only part of the internal professional freedom that Facebook gives.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Creation of pages and groups containing information about the company and its active promotion on social networks. Networks are a form of feedback for your customers and partners. It is a powerful tool that allows you to capture a huge audience that you need at the moment.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The number of users of the social networks Facebook every day only Growth, growth and growth continues. Despite this, I still quite often meet users in networks who are not sufficiently aware of the possibilities of Facebook and the methods of communication not only with participants and partners but also with each other.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What are likes for?",
    answer: "Virtual popularity is what the owners obtain when they want to get Facebook Page Likes. For the sake of fame in the social network, they are ready to wind up and acquire likes. For this, there are entire sites that are intermediaries between those who acquire likes and the performers themselves.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Today, clicking on the \"Like\" button is no ordinary evaluation. It is a service for which there is supply and demand and hence the price.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Interest in a huge number of likes can be not only for people but also companies that want to promote their products or services. It is a certain type of advertising that has become real with the active development of social networks. A product that gets a lot of likes on Facebook inspires customer confidence. Here, different \"I like\" are perceived as advice or a simple call to purchase. The more likes a page has, the higher it ranks in search engine results.",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy Facebook page likes?",
    answer: "Facebook likes cheat – this service is suitable for boosting live likes from active users on any post (photo, video, or message) of a personal profile, group, or FanPage (public). Select a base from the drop-down menu and read a brief description of the base since one base can work exclusively for public page posts, the second for a group, and the third only for a personal profile; pay attention to this.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Facebook likes are used to promote posts on Facebook, increasing the chances of making posts popular by getting into the TOP and recommended blocks. It is possible to get Facebook likes on posts only for open groups/profiles/pages (publics). Check your privacy settings before placing an order to promote a post on Facebook, and you will be able to promote Facebook successfully. Facebook likes 2021-2022 is the best choice for promoting a post.",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Cheat likes on Facebook users for growth and development",
    answer: "A like is an objective indicator of a user's liking and interest in a particular page. It determines the high demand for a specific product: Facebook public likes and Facebook page subscribers.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "After all, they say that the page is not only interesting in terms of content but also reasonable. The logic of the evaluation algorithm is quite clear: users subscribe to the page to follow the news and events, and they give likes when they like what they get.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "t makes the promotion of Facebook pages a profitable and modern solution. Company promotion experts understand the value of likes on a Facebook page and will also help you put it into practice. We offer practical and safe solutions for modern business and promotion.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Buying Facebook likes is your choice if:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You want to create an attractive \"portrait\" of the page\n" +
        "Your goal is to increase sales and awareness of your idea, product, brand, company\n" +
        "You seek to expand your audience reach, increase the activity of subscribers in the Facebook group\n" +
        "You need to achieve high Facebook search rankings\n" +
        "Your priority is a quick start without wasting time and resources\n" +
        "Your task is to promote your Facebook page to generate additional income from advertising.",
    index: 5
  },
  {
    question: "How to get likes on Facebook safely?",
    answer: "The easiest and the safest way to get likes on Facebook is to trust the professionals and place an order on the site, indicating the number of likes you need and a link to the desired post of the public or personal profile. After placing an order, the service will react soon, and likes on Facebook comments will be added to the desired post. Previously, we did not have this service and received dozens of letters with the question: \"How to get Facebook likes on a page or profile in your service?\" But today users and entrepreneurs successfully use this service every day.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, American Express, and Discover, and you may even buy Facebook Page Likes with crypto.",
    index: 6
  }
];

export const spotifyPlaylistFollowersQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Need to buy Spotify Playlist Followers?",
    answer: "Here you can buy real followers at reasonable prices and get the best help you need to be in trends.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "What is Spotify?",
    answer: "It is a music service from developers from Sweden. The app is available in 120 countries. The Spotify digital app has more than 50 million tracks and 4 billion playlists with compositions from foreign and domestic artists in its catalo\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Spotify offers the legal ability to listen to tracks online from a huge music catalog that contains tons of albums, that are not available on other platforms. However, users love the service not only for this.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The main advantage of Spotify is its music selection algorithms, which almost perfectly adapt to the listeners tastes. There are thematic playlists, created by other users and the musicians themselves. Synchronization is conveniently implemented in the service. You can start listening to a track on one device and continue from the same place on another.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Spotify offers artists the largest audience in the world.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Many artists need to put in a lot of musical creativity for users to enjoy their content. It is not easy to stand out from the mass of competitors and stand out among thousands of other artists.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "It is a problem that almost everyone has with Spotify. We have the best solution for this task: real Spotify followers. You can buy Spotify Playlist Followers cheap and easy on Maketop.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What are the types of followers on Spotify?",
    answer: "They are users who have subscribed to you to receive notifications about your new content and be aware of the release of new tracks. Followers in Spotify are per playlist, per profile, and per artist.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Unfortunately, getting followers is extremely difficult. Incredibly talented performers on Spotify often go unnoticed and, due to lack of connections and advertising money, get lost in the crowd. Nothing is impossible in this world, and oblivion and obscurity can turn into popularity and success.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "However, a low number of followers can sow a seed of doubt in the heart of young talent. The expectation of success can last for years, and only the one who never gives up will win!",
    index: 3
  },
  {
    question: "The subtleties of cheating playlist subscribers in Spotify",
    answer: "Thus, getting to the top is a chance for any musician. This achievement will allow you to make yourself known publicly. First of all, success in the application will be beneficial for novice performers who create high-quality content but have not yet received sufficient fame.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Boosting Spotify playlist followers will be a profitable solution for more famous musicians. It will contribute to the development of the track in a shorter time. Thus, buying followers in a Spotify playlist has the following advantages:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "This service is aimed at distributing new products. It is the best option for posting a new song. Customers come here primarily to add new pieces to their playlist that suit their tastes. For this reason, updating the library is of stable interest among followers.\n" +
        "It allows you to increase the royalties. It will be a good investment that will pay off over time.\n" +
        "Getting popular on the resource will help advance your career. A well-known label can notice a good composition, which will be the beginning of a successful career. Such promotion often helps to participate in a festival or event and get into the rotation on the radio.",
    index: 4
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy Spotify Playlist Followers?",
    answer: "Why is it worth contacting us? Maketop offers promotions on Spotify on favorable terms! Thus, cooperation with us has the following advantages:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "The procedure is carried out by professionals who use the most modern and efficient algorithms.\n" +
        "We give a noticeable result in the shortest possible time. It is recommended for those who need quickly declare their creativity!\n" +
        "The service provides a large influx of followers - their number is measured in thousands. The more listeners you have, the more popular the track among real music lovers.\n" +
        "We work with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, and Discover, and you may even buy Spotify Playlist Followers with crypto.\n" +
        "It is also worth noting that the promotion of followers on the Spotify platform is carried out at a favorable and pleasant cost! This service will help you achieve your goals faster and get real profit for your creativity.",
    index: 5
  },

];

export const vkGroupFollowersQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy followers for VK Group?",
    answer: "Buy VK Group followers on our website quickly, easily, and without problems. Reasonable prices will surprise you, and you will be able to promote your group and gain favor.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Maketop suggests buying VK followers on favorable terms. VK is one of the most popular and visited social networks in Runet, the principal competitor of Facebook and Twitter, in terms of the number of participants and user activity.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "VK offers many tools for social interaction: the ability to add friends and ranking them by category. The procedure of quick messages and files, listening to audio files, watching videos, as well as likes, comments, and reposts, make the social network very convenient for communication and entertainment.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy VK Group followers?",
    answer: "VK is also one of the leading social networks in SMM technologies, for example brands and goods promotion in the mass media. Followers who expressed their approval, left comments, and shared information about the product allows you to increase the loyalty of the target audience\n" +
        "\n" +
        "Different tools are used, including the promotion. It can be done by attracting users with catchy headlines, images, material incentives, and using various software methods.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "You can buy followers in VK very easy:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "on the website you will find several widgets that you can click on for quick online orders;\n" +
        "select the appropriate service;\n" +
        "enter your details to process the job;\n" +
        "in a short time, you will see a significant growth in activity in your group.\n" +
        "We are working with different payment providers, including MasterCard, Visa, American Express, Maestro, and Discover, and you may even buy VK Group followers with crypto.",
    index: 2
  }
];

export const vkPostLikesQuestions = [
  {
    question: "Where can you buy cheap Post likes for VK?",
    answer: "Buy VK Post likes of the highest quality and most acceptable cost and enhance your social media account.\n" +
        "\n" +
        "VK is a social space convenient for communication and business, where likes will help improve the demand for a product or service, bring a profile or group to the top, and achieve popularity and a positive attitude.",
    index: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Causes for chasing VK likes",
    answer: "popularity - a direct path to the top VK and recommendations;\n" +
        "increased self-esteem;\n" +
        "trust, the interest of the audience;\n" +
        "growth of VK subscribers;\n" +
        "drawing attention to the published post;\n" +
        "increased interest in buying;\n" +
        "revenue – advertisers will want to buy space for their ads.\n" +
        "Likes have long been an effective tool for attracting the interest of the audience and promoting your own publications.",
    index: 2
  },
  {
    question: "How to buy VK Post likes",
    answer: "The main steps:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "we take the order;\n" +
        "our expert will start working instantly on your page;\n" +
        "you will obtain the first outcomes of our work;\n" +
        "your order will be completed in 3-5 days.\n" +
        "Our benefits:\n" +
        "\n" +
        "User anonymity.\n" +
        "Convenient site design.\n" +
        "Active support.\n" +
        "Constant work on the service.\n" +
        "Our feature is certainly a wide range of benefits and reasonable costs under perfect conditions. If you are considering purchasing VK likes, our site supplies different payment methods. So, you may furthermore buy VK Post likes with crypto.",
    index: 3
  }
];
